Now that we have all of our methods as well as our state,
我们已经编写了所有的方法和状态
what I want to do in this video is just build out
在本视频中
the very minimal UI for both our slider,
我们将为滑块和步进器
as well as our stepper.
构建最基础的 UI
So what we'll do is let's create two more components.
我们再创建两个组件
This one let's call it UdaciSlider.js,
这个叫做 UdaciSlider.js
and then the second one we will call it UdaciSteppers.js.
第二个叫做 UdaciSteppers.js
And then both of these are going to be pretty minimal for now, as I mentioned,
正如我提到的 这两个组件都是最基本的用户界面
so we'll just import react and then let's import view as well as text,
导入 react 并导入 view 和 text
which are both coming from react-native,
都来自 react-native
and both of these are just going to be stateless functional components.
它俩都是无状态函数式组件
We'll say UdaciSlider, and then what we want to return is just a view,
输入 UdaciSlider 返回一个视图
and then we will stick some text inside of it,
在里面放入一些文本
just with the name of the component.
放入组件的名称
I'm just going to copy this and paste it
复制这段代码
into UdaciSteppers because it's going to be similar,
并粘贴到 UdaciSteppers.js 文件中 因为它俩比较相似
and then we will just change the name of the component.
然后更改组件的名称
And then now, inside of AddEntry,
转到 AddEntry
let's go ahead and import both of those.
导入这两个组件
So we get UdaciSlider,
也就是 UdaciSlider
and then we'll also grab UdaciSteppers,
以及 UdaciSteppers
and then now what we want to do is we don't want to just render each of these.
现在我们并不渲染这两个组件
Instead, what we want to do is we want to get the metrics that we care about,
而是获取我们关心的指标
which are those five metrics,
也就是这五个指标
and then what we want to do is we want to either display the slider or the stepper
然后根据该指标对应的类型
depending on the specific type that that metric cares about.
显示滑块或步进器
So what we'll do is inside of our view here,
在这里的视图中
let's do a few things first.
我们先执行几项内容
Let's go ahead, and we will grab
我们将通过调用之前创建的 getMetricMetaInfo
this meta information by just invoking getMetricMetaInfo that we've done before.
获取这个 metaInfo
Then now, what we need to do is,
现在我们输入
let's say, Object.keys pass it metaInfo.
Object.keys() 传入 metaInfo
So this is going to return us an array,
将返回一个数组
which has five properties on it: sleep,
它有五个属性
swim, bike, all those.
swim bike 以及所有这些指标
And then what we want to do is we want to call.map.
然后调用 .map
This is going to be the specific key,
这里将是特定的键
and then from here,
然后在这里
what we want to do is let's go ahead and we will grab getIcon,
从 MetaInfo[key] 获取 getIcon
type, and then everything else from that info[key].
type 以及所有其他内容
Again, what we did is we called getMetricMetaInfo.
这段代码的作用是调用 getMetricMetaInfo
That returned us the whole object,
返回整个对象
which was this whole object right here and then we are mapping overall
也就是这里的整个对象 然后映射它的所有键
of its keys and then we are grabbing each of these properties from the specific key,
并从这个键中获取每个属性
and then we can also grab a value,
获取一个值
which is going to be coming from this.state[key].
该值将来自 this.state[key]
In our example here,
在这里的这个示例中
let's say the first time object.key.map runs,
假设 object.keys.map 第一次运行
key is going to be set to, we'll say run,
key 将设为 run
and so we use getIcon and type coming from metaInfo[run] and
使用来自 metaInfo[run] 的 getIcon 和 type
then we also grab the value which is [this.state[run] and then now,
然后获取值 也就是 this.state[run]
what we want to do is return the same UI.
现在返回一些 UI
We will return, we will say view and because we are in map,
输入 View 因为位于 map 中
we need to go ahead and make sure that we give this a key.
确保提供一个 key
Now, once you use getIcon.
使用 getIcon
If I save this as it is right now,
如果现在保存的话
looks like we have an error on line 48.
似乎第 48 行存在错误
We're missing an equal sign. Let's refresh this.
这里缺少等号 刷新下
You'll notice on both of these now,
你将发现在这两个平台上
we have each of the icons because we have getIcon right here.
都出现了每个图标 因为这里有 getIcon
Now, what we want to do is we either want to show a slider or a steppers.
现在我们将显示滑块或步进器
What we will do as we will say if type equals slider,
如果 type 等于 slider
then what we want to do is we want to render
我们将渲染 UdaciSlider
our UdaciSlider and we want to pass it a few things.
传入几个参数
First, we will pass it the value that we're getting on line
首先将传入在第 49 行获得的 value
49 and then we will pass it an on change function.
然后传入一个 onChange 函数
What this is going to do,
该函数将获得 value
it's going to receive a value and then we will
然后我们将
just call the this.slide, which is this right here.
调用 this.slide 它位于这里
Notice we need to pass it the metric and the value so we can pass it,
注意 我们需要传入 metric 和 value
the key and then the value,
因此传入 key 和 value
and then the last thing we need to pass it is everything else.
然后传入所有其他内容
Now, if it's not a type of slider,
如果不是滑块类型
then what we want to do is we want to render our UdaciSteppers component.
则渲染 UdaciSteppers 组件
This is going to be similar. We're going to pass it a value.
代码很相似 传入 value
We are going to pass it on increments,
传入 onIncrement
which what this is going to do is it's going to call
它将调用 increment 函数
our increment function passing it the specific key or
传入具体的 key
the specific metric and decrement is going to be
也就是具体的指标
the same thing so I'll just copy and paste this and we will change these out.
递减部分也一样 因此复制粘贴这行并稍加修改
This will be decrements.
改为 decrement
Then lastly, we just as before,
最后 和之前一样
want to pass it everything else.
传入所有其他内容
Now, that looks good. Let's see if we have any errors.
看起来正常 看看是否有任何错误
We don't, so you'll notice here that for
没有错误 你会发现
these top three metrics we are getting steppers and for the bottom two,
对于顶部的三个指标 对应的是步进器
we are getting the sliders.
对于底部的两个指标 对应的是滑块